(Bernadette:)And the next wedding gift is...
(Bernadette:)...a gravy boat.
- Oh, one gravy boat.
(Amy:)That's from Sheldon.
He told me he had it engraved.
"In the event of a divorce
please return to Sheldon Cooper."
(Penny:)One inappropriate...
...yet-l-wish-l-thought-of-that
gravy boat.
When I get married, I'm gonna register
at the UCLA cadaver lab.
(Penny:)Ew. Why?
Because I've always wanted
a whole human skeleton...
(Amy:)...and they are really spendy.
(Bernadette:)You actually see you and Sheldon
getting married someday?
(Amy:)Not just someday,
in exactly four years.
(Amy:)But don't tell Sheldon,
he's still a flight risk.
(Bernadette:)What about you, Penny?
(Penny:)What about me, what?
(Bernadette:)Do you think you and Leonard
might ever get married?
(Penny:)Oh, well, you know, Leonard is great.
(Bernadette:)But do you think
you'll ever get married?
(Penny:)He's a sweetie.